{
    "subject": "resource/Nancy_Borlase",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Abstract_impressionism",
    "human_readable": "Nancy Borlase's movement is Abstract Impressionism.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9599221348762512,
            "question": "How does Nancy Borlase's work contribute to the Abstract Impressionism movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8876482844352722,
            "question": "How does Nancy Borlase's work compare to other prominent Abstract Impressionists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7721879482269287,
            "question": "What art movement is Nancy Borlase associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5963522791862488,
            "question": "How does Abstract Impressionism differ from other art movements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5822209715843201,
            "question": "Can you name any specific techniques used by artists in the Abstract Impressionist movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5600609183311462,
            "question": "Can you describe the characteristics of Abstract Impressionism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47684329748153687,
            "question": "What influence has Abstract Impressionism had on contemporary art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4571891129016876,
            "question": "Are there any other artists known for working in Abstract Impressionism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42959433794021606,
            "question": "Where might one find examples of Nancy Borlase's artwork?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42042165994644165,
            "question": "What are some common themes or subjects found in Abstract Impressionist art?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nancy Borlase's movement is Abstract Impressionism.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8491_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might one find examples of Nancy Borlase's artwork?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8491_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other artists known for working in Abstract Impressionism?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8491_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What influence has Abstract Impressionism had on contemporary art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8491_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8491_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Nancy Borlase started as a figurative painter before moving to abstract impressionism, which confirms that her movement is indeed Abstract Impressionism."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Nancy Borlase started as a figurative painter before moving to abstract impressionism, which supports the statement that her movement is Abstract Impressionism."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}